The Mistletoe Inn is a drama, tv movie, romance film directed by Alex Wright.
When aspiring romance novelist Kim Rossi is unceremoniously dumped by her
soon-to-be-published romance novelist boyfriend, Kim takes stock and decides to take a leap.
She signs up for a romance writing retreat at a quaint Vermont Inn shortly before Christmas, where a
top romance novelist is scheduled to attend and read the work of one lucky writer.
Shortly after arriving, she crosses paths with Zeke, whom she initially finds to
be intrusive and, naturally, ends up being her assignment partner.
Worse yet, her ex is also at the retreat.
Despite these bumps in the road, Kim steps outside her comfort zone and
plunges into the writing exercises, surprising herself.
Equally unexpected is the attraction that seems to be building between her and Zeke
that promises to take her down a road she never imagined traveling.
Based on the book by Richard Paul Evans.
Kim, played by Alicia Witt.
Zeke, played by David Alpay.
Garth, played by Casey Manderson.
Samantha, played by Lucie Guest.
Robert, played by Linden Banks.
Luanne, played by Tiffani Timms.
Jill Suzanne Wagner (born January 13, 1979) is an
American actress and television personality.
She was the on-field host for the ABC game show Wipeout from 2008 to 2011 and again
from 2013 to 2014, briefly leaving during the fifth season in 2012.
Since then, Wagner has starred in several made-for-television films for the
Hallmark Channel, Hallmark Movies & Mysteries, and Great American Family.
She stars as Bobby in the Paramount+ spy series Special Ops: Lioness (2023).
The tone is emotional.